losing
I think I caught two.
With first love
Twice as a couple
Because it was concluded
I
i am sorry
In times like this
You should hug me, not my knees.
Just like rice cake
I must have hated the river a lot.
After that, I would have hated my life forever.
I'm so sorry
I've lived better than I thought.
laugh often
There were many times when I was breathtakingly happy.
Write, Park Dal-i
I lived quite well.
Why do you sympathize with me like this?
What happens to your life after five years?
Even if it's short, life is life
no
It's not a pity
I'm so sorry
Um, and don't give me this honor either.
It's awkward
No, how can I do it like before?
Can you treat me poorly?
Not the poverty lecture month.
Please treat me like Bakdal.
like every day
I remember
Not everyone came back
Than the vague past
The five years I lived as Bakdal
Much more vivid
- But...
- and
By any chance, what happens if someone hears it?
I and Gina should be careful with each other.
Huh?
Even with you by my side
I was foolish enough to not recognize
What can I say?
From now on, everything
The moon will do as you say
Bye
I'm just curious.
Why is it lecture month?
Is it bakdal?
No...
No, that, that, what, what...
no, just
I'm just asking.
Which of the two is better?
Please note that both are not possible.
No, what...
This is the answer
Why can't I do this?
foolish me
What can I say?
The moon will do as you say
You're avoiding it, huh? huh?
What can I say, foolish?
- The moon will do as you say.
- A
Ugh!
Are you okay?
Oh, uh, why...
Is it okay for me to be foolish?
The moon will do as you say
Ah, ah...
You were surprised
Mr. Lee
fish oil
foolish me
I'll do this the way I want
Uh, old man.
Elderly!
What is this?
If one Hongyeon goes astray
It's easy for other Hongyeon to go awry too.
That guy is still
It looks like you haven't been able to let go of your regrets.
I didn't even know I was becoming a monster
Eunwolgak Hongnan
I'm in Hanyang with Ganga Yeonwol.
He told me to tell it to the merchant marine.
It's called 'Ganga Yeonwol'
I heard Hongnan has a brother.
Is this the eunuch he ran away from?
How could that...
The unknown group
The word 'life'
I heard they got it tattooed
Ha, please save me, ha
So mama
Compassion and curiosity
It's not something to have carelessly.
The national goal was
I wish I had killed him when he was a year old.
It's the Crown Princess
Killing a military wife
It would have been much easier.
This is also strange
- Please go.
- Ha, let go!
There is that
Seeing as he was dethroned not long after,
That day at my mother's oxygen
I'm sure I saw something I shouldn't have seen
What on earth is on Mt. Gamak?
Come on, I have love for you.
Stop by
There's a temple in front of the place...
Abandoning the status of a court lady and an eunuch
escaped from the palace
Arrest the high treason criminal.
Get out, you bastard
문을 열어라!
- 어
- 추포하라!
- 예!
- 왐마
A day like this will come.
고모!
No, hey, aunt!
Even if the moon is covered with smoke
Can you hide?
Please protect them.
Hey!
the two of you
For getting me caught up in something like this
송구합니다
What can I say
We committed sin
니가 왜 송구햐
yes
nonsense
하지 말아요
Although it ticked once in a while,
I'm sorry
고마웠어요, 고모
owner
혹시나 말이여
다음 생이 있으면
But meet me one more time
그땐 높은 양반
Born as a busy person
With the pottery broken by the hogang
I will build you a mountain
By all means
just one more time
meet me
Ugh
What are you meeting again?
Still, if we ever meet
At that time
Without making a sound
Don't lose your temper
I'll be good to you
- Ugh!
- Stop!
stop
Stop brother!
- Uh, what is it?
- Uh, huh?
- What!
- Father
Get out of the way
Put it on
Father
Tusk, Aunt
Put it on
You, you...
For what reason?
Are you saying they are going to be beheaded?
The queen and eunuch who ran away
I am the sinner who hid them.
That's
This is my family
I will explain it to you.
Please stop bro.
that's not the answer
Please reveal your identity.
If you answer that question
Put it on
Are you even going to let them go?
Who is it!
It's bakdal
Even if you die and wake up, you
Bakdal!
Draw!
I bought it as a bonus anyway
I've been dreaming for five years and that's it
It's the moon
um
For coming to me
Thank you, my daughter
Dear alumni, my daughter
don't cry
Okay?
Execute the sentence!
Ouch!
Stop!
I
I am the abandoned Mr. Kang.
A desolate bin...
폐, 폐...
폐빈, 폐빈 맞아
아, 달이야
Oh no
now
What did you say?
No, moon, no.
It’s the moon, why are you drawing it?
달이야!
- Sweet!
- 달이야!
Didn't you hear?
내가 폐빈 강씨
강가 연월이오
I gave you the answer you wanted
hold on to me
형을 멈추고
Pursue Mr. Kang, a criminal and decommissioned criminal.
- Yes, arrest him!
- Yes
No!
no!
The moon, oh no!
- 어, 달이야!
- Uh, no, no.
달이야!
- No...
- No, it's the moon!
달이야!
Dear Crown Prince!
charge
A desolate person who was sentenced to death
What is alive
This is high treason.
A desolate person who insulted the royal family
Please be true.
How dare you lie about your identity and enter the palace?
A desolate person who insulted the royal family
참하시옵소서!
Please be true.
The moon is not guilty
Don’t you know better than anyone else?
please help
There is no way to exonerate poverty.
The real culprit who killed Jungjeon
Except for confessing
결국 다섯 해 전과
Nothing has changed
Then and now
The most important thing to me is you
charge
broke the order and escaped
Sohun
no
폐빈 강씨를
To be sentenced to death by hanging.
I will uphold your command, Your Majesty.
No, it works
No, your majesty
The Left Wing Committee and Nae Kwan Yoon
Take the Crown Prince to the East Palace.
- Me, Your Highness.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
No, it works
No, your majesty
Let go of this, let go of this!
No, it works!
Please save me from poverty.
No, it works
No, your highness!
Please save me from poverty!
Let go of this!
Are you done now?
Seong Eun-i
I am devastated, Your Majesty.
what does that mean
Sohun Jaga is a poor mother?
So
I didn't believe it either
I'm not the only one who saw it
At the execution site with so many people
Sohun Jagaga
I am Mr. Kang, an abandoned person.
He said it himself.
prepare official uniform
yes
If Sohun is a decommissioned person
What happens to Sohun now?
Your Majesty
I heard that you will be sentenced to death by hanging.
Sohun
No, if the old man dies again
The crown prince can never wake up
Are you worried about me now?
I'm worried
When the crown prince collapses
Someone who will destroy my father
There is no one to find Deokchun for me.
Tell them to bring their wedding clothes.
degradation
Bungungmama’s family
I went back to Unjeong Palace.
Everyone is safe
Yeah, that's a relief.
But what should Mama Bingung do now?
If you command me
Breaking down the prison
We will save the poor woman!
no!
If you move carelessly
I lose Dal again
Never get excited
You must not do anything reckless, sir.
I'll ask for your family.
The situation is the same as five years ago
You have to be cautious
My Majesty, Prince Jeun is here.
Ha, the moon heard the news
Did you hear that?
Yes, together
It's weirder than that
Strange?
I'm on my way from the hospital, and Woohee
I was told to bring a wedding dress.
Is it done?
Yes mama
Yeori will help, so everyone go out.
Mama
Please go out for a moment.
Hmm, if you need help
I'll tell you, come on.
No...
- Wow
- No...
It will end up like this
You came so far away
What are you going to do with me now?
The sentence will be handed down soon.
if you kill me
You are
Do you think you will stay still?
What can you do?
That day at my mother's oxygen
I'm sure I saw something I shouldn't have seen
What on earth is on Mt. Gamak?
Gamak Mountain?
Captain Left is on Mt. Gamak
what are you hiding
I know everything
If I die like this
You will reveal the secret to me.
Anyway, your Majesty or your Majesty
You even thought about seniority.
If you try to reveal bad things
Who would be more nervous?
Mama said
He always urges me to do that.
I wonder if there is anything
I have to tell you about this.
Gabon at once
Aren’t you attaching too much importance to it?
I don't want to get married
The woman who shot the crown prince in the heart
They said they went out and sewed wedding clothes.
Isn’t this strange?
I really have a message
Wow, look at your reasoning skills?
What does it say?
I will escape the villa
please send someone
I'll get your father's attention
Take advantage of that opportunity to let Sohun run away.
When you're ready, make a cuckoo sound
send a signal
I will do it
Mr. Bean could be in danger.
This is my woman
It won't hurt you
yes
degradation
This is at the top of Hanyang
Is this the silk you brought in?
yes, degradation
But how can you say that?
This crude pattern
Do you think it fits the royal family?
Tell the top of Hanyang right away
Please re-deliver after collection.
Ah, yes
Mama, uh, mama
Mama!
Mama, mama
What happened?
He stopped eating and drinking for several days.
It looks like you collapsed.
Contact the internal medicine clinic right away!
don't come
If you come near I will sting you.
- Jericha
- Yes
take off your clothes
I'll go in for a moment
Mama Bin has a villa
They say you escaped.
Is this what Jeundaegun did?
Still sending someone
I checked it.
In the words of Sejak planted in Eunwolgak,
From today noon
I was at Eunwolgak all day.
Who is the abandoned person in prison?
Let me check it out
no
I will check it myself
To the left superior
What's going on?
Just now, he sent his wife to the separate palace.
open the door
yes
Stop!
- under!
- Ha, ha, stop!
under!
Surround!
Save Mr. Bean
Ha!
Catch him!
Mr. Bean comes first!
yes
Mama, are you okay?
mama
Mama, get off quickly.
Mama...
mama
No...
How dare you
Instead of Sohoon, I
I will go to prison
Take Sohun and run away.
Jinga Miryeong, a royal palace belonging to a separate palace
I met the chief left officer, Myeong.
I came to see the abandoned person.
Of course, during shift time
Oh, come in.
Huh?
What is going on here Mr. Bin?
Get out of here and find Deokchun.
Please give me this letter
Chorang Talgeyu?
It was released
no time
Uh, uh, uh, wait a minute
What are you going to do?
human slut
The deceased has run away, find him!
yes!
Now
Let's go
yes
Stop!
Go, go, go, go
- What is all this?
- Yes, Nari.
This is...
This is silk delivered to a clothing store.
I was ordered to repay
I didn't receive any special orders.
I'll check for a moment.
No, wait a minute, here.
The senator is optimistic.
- Get out of the way.
- Ah...
Be careful...
One piece of this silk costs 100 nyang.
If the silk is torn even just a little bit
This whole box
Nari needs to buy it.
One, two, three, four, five
Oh my, this is enough
There is only one tile-roofed house.
How many years has it been since you received the gold medal?
20...
200 years? Oh my
Please check carefully
Hmm, get out now.
Oh my
Thank you, Nari
Go quickly!
You guys, faster
Tell the top of Hanyang right away
Please re-deliver after collection.
Ah, yes...
In the meantime
Does silk catch your eye?
In the meantime, around you
You need to look around carefully.
Ho...
Both you and your poor mother
You left the palace safely.
Good thing
in the end
Nothing has changed from five years ago
Then and now
The most important thing to me is you
To the left
A large private army called the Unknown Corps
I found a situation where
A private soldier?
This is treason
one
Nothing is clear yet
According to this book that Dal-i gave me,
Choraengi mask is in Yangju.
It was said that the unknown group was in Sanchae.
Let's search the nearby mountains
It's just that it's based in Yangju.
I only know this much
Speaking of which,
If I die
Someone else will reveal the secret agreement.
There will be a secret contract there.
I had a left injury the other day.
If you die
It was said that the secret contract will be made public.
Probably
you are the most trustworthy
To the leader of the Unknown Order
must have been hidden
Is there a way?
Go to Jeun and Yangju
I'm thinking of finding the base of the Unknowns.
Ah...
It's something you have to risk your life for.
Are you ready?
no
I have no intention of dying obediently.
five years ago
I disappeared obediently
It's not lecture month.
Leave it alone
I'll never leave
alive
I will live happily for the rest of my time
As if to avenge the past
I will live proudly
It's different from five years ago
yes
Even the poor and the crown prince have changed.
There's no law saying you should stay just because you're overweight.
according to their request
The poor will be hanged
Taking advantage of the moment when Jwasang was distracted,
Take the poor woman and leave the palace.
Abama mama
bring a charm
Yes, Your Highness
take it with you
I'm sorry
I can't always give you strength
cowardly abira
I'll be back
father
Please come quickly, my dear.
Uh, uh, uh...
um
Uh, uh...
Huge
snoring smoke
Isn't it too awkward?
No, Nari
Why did you come now?
I am now...
No, why did you come?
Mr. Bean holding hands
You should definitely run away.
To live
alive
to wait
Woohee
You'll soon realize that I've run away
hurry up
Please take as much time as possible
I'll just go now
Woohee
Wouldn't it be dangerous?
If the bait wants to live
How to miss a fish
I don't know
I don't know anything else
I
How can I leave you behind?
Just like this
Can't you run away with me?
buy
If I get caught again this time
Father is going to kill the great general.
So
Please live, Una.
i will come to you
Ha!
- Let's go
- Yes
Where is the abandoned person?
I don't know
Even if you know
If you're going to let me know
Would you have taken this trouble?
Jericha
W...
Jericho!
Yeori...
Jericha
Even if you kill other connections
Would you blink an eye?
No matter what happens, find the abandoned person.
yes
- Find it!
- yes!
I guess I'm tired too
Hahaha
I ran without resting even for a moment.
go to a nearby village
Should I at least grab a tavern?
Well then
Hey, come to work!
똑바로 봐
이년 알아보려나
보라고, 이 새끼야
똑바로 봐!
let's go
yes
The sun will be setting soon
Huh? Let's stay still
Leisure Mt. Bulgok
Um...
Draw, follow me
Also, there is an amazing thing nearby
I caught a swallow
Huh?
No, what the heck
How many swallows are there?
Come and see me
This house is indie
Yiing
I don't think there's anyone there?
Hey, come in.
Hey, wait a minute.
Are you sure it’s this house?
Can you see the dog here?
This one went out to dig up herbs
That's what it means
Come in.
Is that what this means?
I am thankful that my grandfather saved me the other day.
Be sure to stop by if you come nearby.
I told you
I came home and there was no one there.
Rest in peace
Huh?
I only believe in
Please follow me, ugh.
This way, ha
What does that mean?
I have to go to Gamaksan Mountain.
Actually
The day I was arrested
I sat down and exchanged a few words.
There is an awkward corner
I took a stab at it.
He seemed agitated differently than usual.
Because it really bothers me
Let's go
Please take me to the palace.
Who are you?
This letter
I apologize.
This is our madam.
losing my son
You've lost your mind
Madam
First of all, please at least wear shoes.
the ground is frozen
There was a lot of rudeness
- Please go.
- Ha, let go!
- Mama, looking at your outfit.
- Let go, let go!
It seems like the precious lady is right.
There are no signs of abuse.
I didn't know at the time
I didn't even wear beoseon.
Even the entrance is clean.
Crossing the mountains and crossing the water
It wasn't good
The base of the Unknown Order is on Mt. Gamak.
Does that mean it exists?
Yes, flax oil
and
Above all, Brother Ji
About the woman in white clothing on Mt. Gamak
Did you recognize it?
Well, I'm looking into it.
After closer examination
I'll tell you
About that woman
Aren't you here to tell me?
If something happens to me
Please give this book to me.
What are you saying? What a mess!
Not long after that happened
After being dethroned
The Ji family became extinct.
Gamak Mountain woman in white dress
The unknown band that protects the woman
A book left behind while chasing that woman
something in it
It's clear he left a clue.
Wait a minute
It's a book...
Is that book
Are you sick?
How did you know?
Five years ago in the Senate
I gathered all your things.
But, unusually, I have a medical history.
I remember thinking it was strange
There must be a big clue in there.
I can't enter the palace.
There were black guys everywhere.
Ha, whether it’s Gamaksan Mountain or a palace.
It's dangerous to move right now
First, let's hide for a few days.
yes
- Ah...
- Oh, ah...
where to go
Are you awake?
I'm going to make some breakfast.
Oh no!
What's wrong?
That, my, I do it
Oh, it's okay
What can I do...
Food made by Ji
Is it because you don’t want to eat?
Oh, no, that's not it...
Uh, so
I think I can do it, uh
No, no, no.
I can do it, I can do it
I...
Mr. Lee
The car, one by one, passes by
Not being able to cook is the same thing.
Where, huh?
What are you doing holding a knife?
Come out, I will do it.
- Ha!
- Wow
Why are you so good?
The cutting thing
It was all there.
The only difference is how to write it
What did you cut?
That's like that
That's because it's not easy.
Anyone who does it for the first time can't do it.
Look carefully, this is it
It's never done by force.
It's a trick
Ha!
ah!
Ah...
Uh...
I knew it would be like this
Oh, wait a minute, wow.
To my wife
You can't get rice, huh?
Give it to me
Oh no
If you are that lady
I never eat that rice
It can destroy anything other than firewood well.
Uh oh, oh oh!
Umm
Is it delicious?
Ying
It's delicious
Oh, these walnuts, huh?
It tastes best when eaten with dried persimmons, right?
I guess someone is not a prince
In the midst of all this, are we talking about dried persimmons?
Who wants to eat me?
Something delicious in your mouth
That's because you wanted to put it in, right?
What is it
Chi
Normally I wouldn't know
I hate dried persimmons now.
No, why?
If you go out to look for dried persimmons right now,
'Soon to go' to the underworld
Oh no
It’s a sweltering day at Bam Indy too, huh?
With a message telling me to calm down a bit
I made a joke...
Why are you with a straight face?
us
Should I just run away like this?
What do you mean?
In the sick note left behind by my brother,
About the unknown
There might be a clue.
If not this time too
If you can't overcome the strain even with that,
in the end
If I can't protect you
you are alive like this
we do this
I'm smiling while looking at you
Revenge or righteousness?
What's the use of it all?
I will live as your own river
we just
Can't we live like that?
Ha, if there is no crown prince
The next successor is Prince Jeun.
Prince Jeun succeeds the throne
No matter what happens, we have to stop it
Still
I'm Mama's only blood relative.
Prince Jeun more than anyone else
It might be better to sit on the dragon podium...
I
To Jeundaegun’s mother
Fraudulently accused of adultery and killed
The great prince was driven out to Sinjusa Temple.
That guy is in that black
What kind of intentions are you hiding?
who knows
Ha, never
He shouldn't be sitting on the dragon podium.
mama
Actually
Circulating secretly among courtiers
I heard a rumor...
Where is the left statue?
a while ago
Mr. Bin and Prince Jeun
The fact that I ran away at night
I know
Did you call me to scare me?
I called to make a deal.
Even if you can't find the crown prince
The reason Prince Jeun climbs the dragon statue is
Stop it
Prince Jeundae
Aren’t you Mama’s only blood relative?
I have never seen that child
I never thought of you as my grandchild.
Queen Jangjeong gives birth to a son
When the son becomes crown prince, the previous king
The prophecy that I cannot fulfill my command
It became real
Prince Jeundae
I shouldn't have been born
No, in the first place
Queen Jangjeong
Such an unclean woman
It wasn't made to sit in the middle palace.
The royal family's misfortune
Today's tragedy is all
It's because of that hat.
But to Prince Jeun
The thing that makes the dragon turn
That doesn't make sense
Mama said
Nothing has changed
I thought I took it all
What do you want to protect?
Are you still angry?
You took everything
What...
calm down
It's a bitch
Do you think it is because of the prophecy?
Still with Queen Jangjeong
You're blaming it on Prince Jeundae.
The work of the Year of the Pig
It's because of mama
Why did you do that to Queen Jangjeong!
Oh my mom
Oh my!
Let's count...
Absolutely Abama
Don't blame me
These eyes, nose and lips
From fingertips to toes
It's all given to me by Abama.
Oh my mom
Oh my!
Oh, no way...
for what reason
That precious woman
Fraudulent accusation of adultery
I killed you.
Is it because of me?
Hani
In that mouth again
Queen Jangjeong's mama
don't raise
I'm going to the Qing Dynasty
It's me and my two in-laws
Until tomorrow at Shinsi
Please help me find a boat to go to Jemulpo.
Yes, I understand, Nari.
Oh, I...
Huh?
100, 100 nyang?
Oh, oh, oh
Your Majesty sent
Make up for the decline
He tells us to complete our cause.
no
How did you find out about this place?
I searched all over this area.
Uh, uh...
Oh, I'm here, I'm here!
Please give me a poor person
Please leave now, sir.
You don’t like it?
Even by using force
I received an order to bring you.
Oh, really?
Take the moon with you
It's a person
- degradation
- How can you tell me to leave you alone?
Go quickly!
From now on
I do what I want
- Degradation!
- degradation
Yeah, come and see.
I dream of sitting on a ball or something.
If you want to make bubbles
Come on!
What are you doing? I didn't pave the way
Make a way
Hey Gayu
yes
Geun-di-yu, low-grade
If only we were happy together
Should I stop?
Mr. Bean too
Jeundaegun Nari Island
Even your Majesty is anxiously waiting.
I only trust you and me
many people waiting
I throw it all away and leave.
Will we be happy?
The left injury continues
I would live doing bad things
We haven't sinned
Living while running away
Isn’t that too much of a loss?
Let’s do business
I just hate losing money
Inside Gamaksan Mountain
Is there a base for the Unknowns?
And is there a secret contract in it?
I can't be sure of anything.
You have to grasp at straws.
Just in case it's there, I'll go and see it.
This is Bae Soo-jin, who is opening now.
It's a gambling table
If there's one thing you can do
Even if you can’t eat, go straight
Even if I can’t see ahead
Expect a frontal breakthrough
yes
I'll do as you say
Jeungyeongsa Temple on Mt. Gamak
There is a temple
- I'll wait there...
- No, I'm coming.
I need to go to the palace and get my medical records.
I thought changing my body was a curse
maybe
very good opportunity
It could be possible
I don't know how to fight, so I'm going alive
Because you have good quick wits
Go to the palace and find the military record.
As soon as I left, my feet were tied up.
It won't be easy though
Be sure to find it and send it through luck
This is
do as i say
Yes
Uh, low, low, low
His Majesty has issued an order to ban family
Ah, but what is that?
I wonder what you mean, Your Majesty?
If it's forbidden, you'll be trapped without a move.
Oh, I borrowed it from Prince Jeun.
I guess I should return Sun Tzu’s Art of War.
- It's in the closet.
- Boy, does that matter now?
In the past
Gamaksan Jeungyeongsa Temple
Do you remember the moon you saw in?
Why are you suddenly talking about me and the moon?
still there
The moon will stay
Give the book back to Jaune
I'm talking about illness.
Oh!
Oooh, oh
‘The Art of War’?
That's right, that's right
My brother read this book
You told me to deliver it to you?
yes
Ah
This hobu and seen from Jeungyeongsa Temple on Mt. Gamak
You talked about the moon.
But I
With me
I don’t remember going to Gamaksan Mountain.
If it's 'the moon'...
'It's still there
He said, “The moon stays.”
Poor mother
I guess that means you are at Jeungyeongsa Temple?
It's just a sick note
What's different?
It's different
written in the sick record
I found the location of Unmyungdan Sanchae.
I will be back within three days at the latest.
Nameless group, wild vegetables?
Six years ago, on Mt. Gamak
With this white woman
I saw the unknown group.
Let it go, let it go!
Wait a minute
white suit woman
letter
soon
They say a ban on marriage will be issued.
Daenggi’s
I passed the military exam
When I'm strong enough to protect you
Can I talk to you then?
Can't I live?
please live
Please live
This is my son
I am now
I have become infinitely stronger
There's no way for you to come back
To me
What should I do?
Security is tight over there too.
It's suspicious.
Yo
Finding out up close
I think it would be good
It's a left injury
mother
Where Mama is
There must be a secret contract.
When you find the secret contract
Holding that secret contract
Go straight to Hanyang
Could you please go?
Chief Justice Kim Han-cheol's wife's meal
I appoint you crown princess.
Father
Because you broke me
I am in pieces
I have no choice but to stab my father.
I said I would come, so I said I would come.
I will definitely come
This is me and the moon
It's our revenge